findnsave.com 2019-07-07

# Find&Save | Privacy Policy

## Last Updated: December 11, 2017

Protecting your privacy is really important to FindnSave. Accordingly, we're providing this Privacy Policy to explain our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive when you use our Services (as defined in our Terms of Service, accessible at www.findnsave.com/terms). This Privacy Policy applies only to those services and Apps included within “Services” and doesn't apply to any third-party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible through our Services. 

AS NOTED IN OUR TERMS OF SERVICE, WHEN YOU ACCESS THE SERVICES VIA THE FINDNSAVE-BRANDED SECTION OF A THIRD PARTY WEBSITE, ADDITIONAL THIRD PARTY TERMS MAY GOVERN YOUR USE OF THE THIRD PARTY WEBSITE ITSELF. IF YOU PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO THE THIRD PARTY WEBSITES, THEN THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF THE THIRD PARTY WEBSITES GOVERN THE THIRD PARTIES' USE OF THAT INFORMATION. FINDNSAVE IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE THIRD PARTY WEBSITES OR THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF ANY SUCH THIRD PARTIES AND DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY IN THIS REGARD. 

Also, please note that, unless we define a term in this Privacy Policy, all capitalized words used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service. 

## How do we collect and use information?

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, to administer your use of the Services (including your Account, if you are an Account holder), and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our Services. 

### Location Information.

In some cases (such as in connection with the Incentive Campaigns) we collect and store information about where you are located, such as by accessing the GPS information available through your mobile device, if you permit us to do so, so that we can offer certain types of Incentive Campaigns to you. We may also use location information to improve and personalize our Services for you. 

### Account Information.

When you create an Account, we'll collect certain information that can be used to identify you, such as your name email address, and physical address ("Personally Identifiable Information" or "PII").. 

We may also collect certain information that is not PII because it cannot be used by itself to identify you, such as your age, gender and items you "like", "save" or "follow" via the Services. If you choose to create an Account through one of your SNS Accounts, you may have to provide us with your username (or userID) so that your identity can be authenticated by the SNS Account. When the authentication is complete, we'll be able to link your Account with the SNS Account and access certain PII, such as your name and email address, and other PII that your privacy settings on the SNS Account permit us to access. We don't receive or store passwords for any of your SNS Accounts. 

By creating an Account you agree that we may use any email address associated with your Account, including without limitation email addresses associated with one of your related SNS Accounts, to send you emails related to the Services. These emails may include offers from FindnSave partners and affiliates. If you want to change your email preferences you must first log into your Account at findnsave.com and you may change your email preferences by visiting findnsave.com/settings.

### Information Collected Using Cookies.

We collect certain information through the use of "cookies," which are small text files that are saved by your browser when you access our Services. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to identify that you've logged in to the Services and to tell us how and when you interact with our Services. We may also use cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Services and to customize and improve our Services. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted when you log off from the Services and close your browser. Although most browsers automatically accept cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies. Please note, however, that if you don't accept cookies, you may not be able to access all portions or features of the Services. Some third-party services providers that we engage (including third-party advertisers) may also place their own cookies on your browser. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of cookies and does not include use of cookies by such third parties. 

### Information Related to Use of the Services.

Our servers automatically record certain information about how a person uses our Services (we refer to this information as  **"Log Data"** ), including both Account holders and non-Account holders (either, a  **"User"** ). Log Data may include information such as a User's Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the web page that a User was visiting before accessing features of our Services, the pages or features of our Services to which a User browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, search terms, the links on our Services that a User clicked on and other statistics. We use this information to administer the Services and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) this information to improve and enhance the Services by expanding their features and functionality and tailoring them to our Users' needs and preferences. 

### Information Sent by Your Mobile Device.

We collect certain information that your mobile device sends when you use our Services, like a device identifier, user settings, and the operating system, as well as information about your use of our Services. 

### Promotions.

From time to time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions (collectively, "Promotions") offered via the Services. If you decide to participate, we will request certain PII from you. Participation in these Promotions is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We use this information to administer your participation in each Promotion. 

## What Information Do We Share With Third Parties?

We may share information that we have collected from you, including PII, as described below: 

### Advertising Services

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you use our Services. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use both personally identifiable information (e.g., your name, phone number, physical or electronic address) and non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at www.aboutads.info or Networking Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Company who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of their personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. You may request a list of all of the third parties with whom we share your PII by sending an e-mail to [support@wanderful.com](mailto:support@wanderful.com) and place “California Third Party Disclosure” in the subject line. Please allow up to thirty days for a response.

### FindnSave Users.

If you choose to create an Account, other Users may be able to view items that you list or "like" via the Services in connection with your name, city and state. You may mark your lists and items in your lists as "private" via the Services, in which case such lists will not be viewable by other Users. We recommend that you guard your sensitive information. 

### Information Shared with Our Services Providers.

We may engage third party service providers to work with us to administer and provide the Services. These third-party services providers have access to your PII only for the purpose of performing services on our behalf. 

### Information Shared with Third Parties.

We may share information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other similar purposes. 

### Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions.

Information that we collect from our users, including PII, is considered to be a business asset. As a result, if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy or if we are acquired as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your PII may be disclosed or transferred to the third-party acquirer in connection with the transaction. 

### Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others.

It is our policy to protect you from having your privacy violated through abuse of the legal systems, whether by individuals, entities or government, and to contest claims that we believe to be invalid under applicable law. However, it is also our policy to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties. Accordingly, we reserve the right to disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary: (i) to satisfy or comply with any applicable law, regulation or legal process or to respond to lawful requests, including subpoenas, warrants or court orders; (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the rights, property and safety of third parties or the public in general; and (iii) to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. 

### Information We Disclose With Your Consent or at Your Request.

We will share your PII and information contained in your Account with third-party sites or platforms in accordance with the selections you make via the Services. 

## The Security of Your Information

We take reasonable measures to protect the information that we collect from or about you (including your PII) from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information. 

## Links to Other Sites

Our Services may contain links to other websites and services. Any information that you provide on or to a third-party website or service is provided directly to the owner of the website or service and is subject to that party's privacy policy, including as noted above, the third party website in which there is a Findnsave-branded section. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or services and we're not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of those websites or services. To protect your information we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of other websites and services that you access. 

## Modifying Your Information

You can access and modify the PII associated with your Account via the "Edit Profile" section of the Services. If you want us to delete your PII and your Account, please contact us at [support@findnsave.com](mailto:support@findnsave.com) with your request. We'll take steps to delete your information as soon as is practicable, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law. 

## International Transfer

Your PII may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you're located outside the United States and choose to provide your PII to us, we may transfer your PII to the United States and process it there. 

## Our Policy Toward Children

Our Services are not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected PII of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible. 

## Changes to Privacy Policy

Any information that we collect is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we'll notify you of such changes by posting them on the Services or by sending you an email or other notification, and we'll indicate when such changes will become effective. 

## Questions?

Please contact us at OwnLocal Inc., 205 W. 9th Street, Austin, TX 78701 or via email at [support@findnsave.com](mailto:support@findnsave.com) if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy. 

Thank you! 

We'll Review this offer and take the appropriate actions.  
We appreciate you helping us make Find&Save the best shopping experience around. 

\- The Find&Save Team
